Business Ephemera Collection
Hartford History Center, Hartford Public Library
- Billheads, Invoices, Letterheads, Receipts
  - Advertisement, Brown, Thomson & Company, 1894; Special Offer of a Bicycle, the Tourist Light Roadster with Bidwell Pneumatic Tires (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Advertisement, Brown, Thomson & Company, 191-; Brochure advertising Meccano, "The best toy for any boy" (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Advertisement, Bruce Filley & Company, 189-; Advertisement for Quaker ranges (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Receipt, Burkett & Ives "The Bee Hive", 1868; Invoice for tassels, curtains, table covering, dress goods, blankets, etc. purchased by Edward Miller (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Receipt, Burkett & Ives "The Bee Hive", 1868; Invoice for rug and carpet purchased by Edward Miller (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Invoice, C.S. Brewer & Company, 1897; Invoice for sugar and Grenoble walnuts purchased by A. K. and P. Talcott (Box 7)
  - Receipt, C.S. Weatherby & Company, 1864; Receipt for items purchased by J. S. Finney (Box 7)
  - Receipt, C. Smith & Co., 1852; Receipt for cotton batts purchased by Chauncey Gaines (Box 7)
  - Receipt, Capewell Horse Nail Company, 1911; Letter noting receipt of payment from Brockett & Strong, Windham, New York (Box 7)
  - Letter, Capitol Bedding Company, 1945; Letter to First National Bank of Hartford requesting renewal of insurance on building at 479 Windsor Street (Box 7)
  - Envelope, Capitol City Lumber Company, 192-?; Envelope with advertisement for lumber company (Box 7)
  - Stock certificate, Carleton Foundry Company, 1899; Certificate issued to William H. Watrous (Box 7)
  - List, Clark & Co., 18--; List of carriage makers' hardware, including axles and springs (Box 7)
  - List, Clark & Co., 18--; List of products in stock including small flat iron and large flat iron (Box 7)
  - Receipt, Clark & Co., 1875, 1878; Two receipts for items purchased by J. S. Corban (Box 7)
  - Receipt, Clark, Gill & Company, 1845; Receipt for nails purchased by Foster & Co. (Box 7)
  - Invoice, Clayton Motors, Inc., 1953; Invoice for a 1951 Chevrolet sold to Henry L. Creelman, Jr. (Box 7)
  - Invoice, Dall & Bowers, 191-; Blank invoice (Box 7)
  - Invoice, E. & R. Terry, 1833; Invoice for tea, tobacco, raisins, candles, sugar, cloves, etc. purchased by Sterling Chapin (Box 7)
  - Receipt, Edwin Hunt, 1846; Receipt for psalter and psalms (Box 7)
  - Stock certificate, Etna Peat Company, 186-; Twenty stock certificate for shares in Etna Peat Company. Printed by Bingham & Dodd. (Box 7)
  - Receipts, Ezra Clark & Company, 1851, 1853; Two receipts for nails purchased by Foster & Co. (Box 7)
  - Receipt, Farnham & Barnes, 1861; Receipt for items purchased by E. W. Webster (Box 7)
  - Letter, Fernside Manufacturing Company, 1902; Letter to Farr Alpaca Company, Holyoke, Massachusetts regarding Fernside clamp (Box 7)
  - Invoice, Foster & Co., 1881; Invoice for tobacco purchased from the Buckeye Tobacco Works (Box 7)
  - Promissory notes, Foster & Co., 1856, 1859; Three promissaory notes dated 1856 and 1859. Printed by Elihu Geer, 16 State Street, Hartford. (Box 7)
  - Advertisement, Geeley Wardrobe, 1882; Four-page flier with advertisements for clothing and brief history of firm (Box 7)
  - Invoice, Gengras Motors, Inc., 1958; Invoice for 1957 Ford Fairlane 500 sold to Henry L. Creelman (Box 7)
  - Receipt, George M. May & Company, 1855; Receipt for tobacco [?] purchased by Chauncey Gaines (Box 7)
  - Stock certificate, Gray Manufacturing Company, 1969; Stock certificate issued to Newburger Loeb & Co. Includes an illustration of a pay telephone (Box 7)
  - Letter, H. & D. Daniel, 1909; Letter to H. A. Hull, Counselors-at-Law regarding a building in New London, Connecticut (Box 7)
  - Advertisement, Hartford Braided Wire Mattress Company, 1879; Advertisement in the form of a promotional letter soliciting orders (Box 7)
  - Agreement, Hartford Cycle Company, 189-; Blank contract between Hartford Cycle Company and agent (Box 7)
  - Receipts, Hartford Mill & Manufacturing Company, 1848-1849; Six receipts for items purchased by Foster & Co. Image of Hartford Steam Mill signed "Lith of Alden & Kuchel" (Box 7)
  - Advertisement, Hartford One Price Clothing Company, 18--; Colored print of a Neapolitan boatman, a young woman and child (Box 7)
  - Invoice, Henry Lewis & Company, 1884; Invoice for overalls, pants, boots, suit for a boy, shirt, socks, hat, wrapper, etc. purchased by I. W. Strong (Box 7)
  - Brochure, Horsfall & Rothschild, 1907; Brochure advertising ladies' furs (Box 7)
  - Receipts, Imlay & Smith, 1846-1847; Two receipts for flour sold to E. R. Swift (Box 7)
  - Invoice, Irad Edwards & Son, 1869; Invoice for butter crackers, soda crackers, etc. purchased by A. K. Talcott (Box 7)
  - Receipt, Isaac G. Allen, 1844; Invoice for overalls, pants, boots, suit for a boy, shirt, socks, hat, wrapper, etc. purchased by I. W. Strong (Box 7)
  - Receipt, John Olmsted & Company, 1840; Receipt for calico and yarn (Box 7)
  - Receipt, John Olmsted & Company, 1840; Receipt for calico and yarn (Box 7)
  - Receipt, Joseph G. Lane, 1888; Receipt or sugar puchased by Foster & Co. (Box 7)
  - Advertisement, Kenyon's Tea, Coffee and Spice House, 188-; Advertisement, possibly originally with a calendar affixed to the lower portion (Box 7)
  - Receipt, L.B. Sill, 1897; Invoice for 2 dozen pipes sold to J. A. Alvord, Manchester, Connecticut (Box 7)
  - Price list, L.Barker & Company, 1879; "Bulletin of New Music" listing songs and instrumental music (Box 7)
  - Letter, Lincoln & Company, 1897; Letter to Farr Alpaca Company, Holyoke, Massachusetts, regarding payment due (Box 7)
  - Letter, Lincoln & Company, 1899; Letter to Farr Alpaca Company, Holyoke, Massachusetts, regarding payment (Box 7)
  - Brochure, Ludlow Barker & Company, 1886; Advertising brochure with poem "The Music Household." (Box 7)
  - Letter, Mahoney Grocery, 1905; Letter to Mr. Clark regarding payment (Box 7)
  - Letter, Merrow Machine Company, 1944; Letter to First National Bank of Hartford requesting a receipt (Box 7)
  - Receipt, N.B. Bull & Son, 1892; Invoice for tin, soldering, and hours worked made out to the Hartford and Wethersfield Street Rail Road Company (Box 7)
  - Receipt, N.B. Bull & Son, 1895; Invoice for iron, lead pipes, and labor made out to the Hartford Street Rail Road Company (Box 7)
  - Advertisement, Norman Smith, 1842; Broadside advertising chimney flues invented and patented by Smith (Box 7)
  - Invoice, Otto Epstein, Inc., 1919; Invoice for installing tank in a house on Barbour Street for Trustees of Keney Park (Box 7)
  - Advertisement, Patent Chrn-Dash Company, 186-; Description and price list for an improved butter churn (Box 7)
  - Receipt, Perkins Electric Lamp Company, 1892; Receipt from Charles N. Knox, Agent made out to J. K. Lanman for purchase of light bulbs (Box 7)
  - Letter, Perkins Electric Lamp Company, 1889; Letter regarding the sale of property (Box 7)
  - Advertisement, Pitkin Brothers & Company, 189-?; Advertisement soliciting patronage (Box 7)
  - Catalog, Post & Lester Company, 1903; List of lubricants for use in engines, including automobile engines, with testimonials from automobile manufacturers (Box 7)
  - Receipt, Putnam Phalanx Market, 1876; Receipt for steaks, potatoes, cucumbers, peas, etc. purchased by A. N. Hathaway (Box 7)
  - Receipt, R.D. Hawley, 1874; Receipt for brooms (?) purchased by Hartford and Wethersfield Horse Railway Company (Box 7)
  - Receipts, R.P. Kenyon & Company, 1875; Two receipts for caps and hats puchased by C. L. Clark (Box 7)
  - Receipts, R.P. Kenyon & Company, 1878; Two receipts for caps and hats puchased by C. L. Clark (Box 7)
  - Letter, R.P. Kenyon & Company, 1878; Letter to "Friend Chas." (C. L. Clark?) regarding initial to be stamped on buttons (Box 7)
  - Receipt, Ripley & Cune, 1840; Receipt for one cask of nails purchased by Mr. Howe (Box 7)
  - Advertisement, Robert Walker's Art Store, 188-; Advertising flier with directions for mixing oil paints (Box 7)
  - Receipt, Rodney Kellogg, 1860; Invoice for slaked lime, axe handle, whip lash, and paper sage purchased by Mr. Talcott (Box 7)
  - Receipt, Sage-Allen, 1993; Cash register receipt for purchases (Box 7)
  - Invoice, Seyms & Company, 1903; Invoice for beef and cigars sold to C. L. Clark (Box 7)
  - Letter, Skat Co., 1931; Letter to Dublic Tractor Company, Willimantic, stating that the sand they provided is too dark and cannot be used (Box 7)
  - Labels, Jessie G. Smith, n.d.; Six labels reading "Genuine Pomatum Manufactured by Jesse G. Smith, Hartford, Conn." (Box 7)
  - Letter, Smith, Northam & Company, 1886; Letter to the administrator of the I. W. Strong estate enclosing statement of account (Box 7)
  - Invoice, Smith, Northam & Company, 1892; Invoice for products purchased by C. L. Clark (Box 7)
  - Invoice, Smith, Northam & Company, 1897; Invoice for 8 bushels of "Surprise" purchased by J. A. Alvord (Box 7)
  - Receipt, Smith-Worthington Company, 1913; Invoice for reins, bits, bridles, collars, and carriage top dressing sold to C. M. Beach, New Milford, Connecticut (Box 7)
  - Catalog, Strauss Stores, 1955; Illustrated spring and summer catalog featuring automobile paint, picnic grills, lawn mowers, garden hose, etc. (Box 7)
  - Receipt, T.M. Allyn, 1848; Receipt for two bales of wick purchased by Gilbert & Swift (Box 7)
  - Invoice, W.N. Pelton & Company, 1888; Invoice for vests, mittens, braid, corsets, thread, etc. made out Warner & Clark (Box 7)
  - Invoice, Weatherby, Knous & Pelton, 18--; Invoice for "Misc." purchased by D. W. Norton (Box 7)
  - Invoice, Weatherby, Knous & Pelton, 18--; Invoice for cotton, calico, etc. purchased by George W. [?]. Invoice printed by Bingham & Dodd (Box 7)
  - Advertisement, Wilcox Brothers, 1878; Description of cow fetter and testimonials from satisfied customers (Box 7)
  - Invoice, William H. Bulkeley & Co. "The Bee Hive", 1888; Invoice for borders, embroideries, etc. purchased by Warner & Clark (Box 7)
  - Invoice, William H. Post & Company, 1888; Invoice for shades, etc. made out to F. D. Worth (Box 7)
  - Advertisement, Williams Brothers Golden Horse Market, 1919; Postcard describing horses for sale, soliciting orders by mail or telephone. Postcard printed by Calhoun Press. (Box 7)
  - Receipt, Woodruff & Beach, 1859; Receipt for a pulley purchased by E. W. Webster (Box 7)
  - Receipt, Z.B. Heywood, 187-; Receipt for $51.30 of "merchandise" purchased by Pomroy & Mather (Box 7)
- Trade cards, Business Cards, Miscellaneous Small Advertisements
  - Postcard, Acorn Studio, 199-; Mary Crombie (Geer) (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, Thomas Adams Marble Factory, "American and foreign monuments of various designs" (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, Adams House, S. Adams, Proprietor. "Opposite the Trotting Park" (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, M. Adler & Son, 187-?; "C.B.D. Clothing House" Six different comic designs (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Business card, Advest, Inc, 198-?; Business card of Douglas T. Putnam, Vice President (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, Aetna Insurance Company, J. B. Bennett, General Agent, Cincinati, Ohio (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Business card, Aids Project Hartford, 198-?; Patricia C. Root, Executive Director (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, Aishberg's Shoe Store, 186-?; "First Class Boots and Shoes at Low Prices." Three different designs. (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, Al-Di-La Restaurant, 197-; "European Service. Food for the Epicure." (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, Algiers, 1944?; "Meet Ralph Mixer as Sketched by Johnny Anderson in The Hartford Times." (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, Allen Brothers, 1880?; "I could live in a desert, if only with thee." (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, Allen Paper Company, 18--?; Six different floral designs, one card with a portrait of Abraham Lincoln, printed by Bufford. (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, James P. Allen, Boarding, Sale, and Livery Stable, 186-?; "The largest and most complete stable in the city." (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, James P. Allen, Boarding, Sale, and Livery Stable, 187-?; "Having completed extensive improvements, I have now one of the finest stables in New England." (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, Allen's Market, 187-?; Three different comic designs (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, Allyn & Blanchard, 188-; "Enterprise Breakfast Coffee" Printed by Bufford, Boston. (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, Allyn, Blanchard & Latimer, 188-?; "Perfect Roasted Coffee. The Roasted Berry, not ground." Eight different designs illustrating the story of Bluebeard, printed by Bingham & Dodd. (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, Allyn, Blanchard & Latimer, 188-?; "We wish to make you acquainted with our 'Quakeress' (Cigar) warranted to please…." (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, Allyn House, 185-?; Includes timetable for city railroad and stage routes "No Stages on the Sabbath." (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, Allyn House Boot and Shoe Store, 185-?; John Watson, Proprietor. O.W. Chaffee, Superintendant. Printed by Calhoun Printing Works. (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Business card, American Automobile Association, 198-; Joan Matthews, Member Services Counselor (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, American Hotel, E. Foster, Proprietor. "Pleasantly situated" (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, American Tea Company, P. H. Quinn, Proprietor. "Spices of the best quality" Three different floral designs (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, American Tea Company, P. H. Quinn, Proprietor. "5 lbs. Good Coffee for $1" - Five different floral designs (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, American Tea Company, P. H. Quinn, Proprietor. "13 lbs. Sugar for $1" Two different floral designs (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, American Tea Company, P. H. Quinn, Proprietor. "Teas, Coffees, Sugars, Spices, &c." Three different floral designs (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Postcard, F.S. Amidon, 19--?; "Hopkins' Union Bitters and Amidon's Union Ginger Brandy and Cordials." Three designs depicting bathing beauty, courting couple, and sexual harrassment. (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Business card, Amsafe Security Systems, 198-?; Business card of Bruce M. Simons, Security Consultant (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, Andrus & Naedele Company, 189-?; "Dealers in Shot Guns, Rifles, Pistols, Fishing Tackle and a General Line of Sporting Goods" (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, Arcade, "5, 10 & 25c Goods a Specialty". THREE copies printed on different color card stock (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, Mrs. H.L. Arnold, 187-?; "I have a full assortment of the latest styles and novelties in Millinery, which I offer at lowest living prices…" Printed by Bufford, Boston. (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, Arnstein, Loth & Hartman, 1861; "Manufacturers of Cloaks and Mantillas." (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, Atlas Cabinet Works, 192-; Charles F. Dettenborn, Proprietor. (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, Charles Avery's boot and Shoe Store, "Glycerole for Oiling & Dressing Ladies' Shoes." (Box 8, Folder A)
  - Trade card, William A. Bacon & Son, 1864?; "Glycerole for Oiling & Dressing Ladies' Shoes." (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, Baldwin, Downing and Company, 186-?; "Teams constantly in readiness for Transportation of all kinds of Merchandise to or from Cars and Boats and about Town." Two copies. (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, B. Ballerstein, 1876?; "Buy Your Holiday Goods from B. Ballerstein." (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, B. Ballerstein and Company, 187-?; Six designs all featuring children and flowers (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, B. Ballerstein and Company, 187-?; Cut-out of a basket of flowers "Compliments of R. Ballerstein & Co…." (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, B. Ballerstein and Company, 187-?; "Hartford Millinery Emporium" (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, B. Ballerstein and Company, 187-?; Design featuring two little girls with butterfly nets (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, B. Ballerstein and Company, 1880; "The Hartford Milliners": Design featuring a moth (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, B. Ballerstein and Company, 1880; "The Hartford Milliners": Design featuring a moth (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Postcard, Edward B. Barker, 19--; Two postcards depicting "The Old 'Tin Bridge' near Farmington, Conn." based on a photograph by E. N. S. One card printed in black, the other in sepia. (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, L. Barker & Company, 185-; "Examine the Ivers & Pond Pianos. Matchless in Tone." Two different designs featuring children. (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, Barker & Gaines, 1881?; "Genuine New Haven Rolling Spring Bed! Sold Only by Barker & Gaines…." Two different designs featuring humorous old men. (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, Barker & Kellogg, 1882; "New Home Sewing Machine Co. Orange, Mass. 30 Union Sq. New York." Two cards with different designs each featuring a woman on a path in front of a house." (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, Barker & Kellogg, 188-?; Trade card in the shape of a book (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, Barker & Kellogg, 1882; "New Home Sewing Machine!" Two different designs: "What are the Wild Waves Saying" and "The Monkey and the Cat's Paw." (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, J.R. Barlow, 187-; Two different designs (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, Mrs. M.M. Barnum, 189-? (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Bookmark, S.W. Barrows and Company, 187-; Three different designs featuring birds and birdcages (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Bookmark, S.W. Barrows and Company, 187-; Four different designs featuring cupids (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, S.W. Barrows and Company, 187-; One design featuring butterflies (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, S.W. Barrows and Company, 187-; Twelve cards representing the twelve months. Text in French. (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, S.W. Barrows and Company, 187-; Six cards depicting dancing children in costume entitled "Bal d'Enfant." (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, S.W. Barrows and Company, 187-; Six cards, with four different designs depicting costumed frogs (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, S.W. Barrows and Company, 187-; Five cards featuring children (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, S.W. Barrows and Company, 188-?; "Dealers in Birthday, Easter and Business Cards." (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, George D. Bartlett and Company, 1868?; "Winter has Come! Owing to the dullness of our Wholesale Trade, we have too much clothing on hand…." (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, "Bee-Hive", 186-?; "Where Dry Goods, Carpets and Paper Hangings are sold cheap by Starr, Burkett & Co." (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, "Bee-Hive", 1879; "The Great Holiday Sale Commencing Dec. 10 1879" "Headquarters of Santa Claus" Two copies (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, "Bee-Hive", 1886?; "Presented by the Bee Hive" a magnificent Emporium…." Printed by The Kellogg & Bulkeley Co. Two copies. (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Postcard, E.L. Beerwort, Inc., 1954; "See the all-new Strong-Arm Hoists--3 ways today's greatest hoist value…" (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, Thomas H. Belden, 186-?; "New and Second Hand Goods…. Money to Lend on the above and other personal property…." (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, A. Bernheimer, 18--?; "Manufacturer and Dealer in All Kinds of Clothing" (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, F. Bestor, 18--; "Bestor's Golden Quill Stub Pens, made of the finest Silver Steel, having a Golden finish…." Two copies printed on different colored cardstock (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, E.S. Bill, 18--; "Bestor's Golden Quill Stub Pens, made of the finest Silver Steel, having a Golden finish…." Two copies printed on different colored cardstock"Good Luck to all who Trade with E. S. Bill, Agt." 2 copies. (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, G. Edward Bishop, "Teacher of the Violin, All Brass Valve Instruments, and Military Bands. Music Arranged or Copied for Orchestras, Military Bands, Church Choirs, Etc." (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, H. & S. Bissell, 1860; "Manufactory on Charter Oak Avenue, near Colt's Pistol Works." includes Price List. (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, S.T. Bissell, 187-?; "Agent for Decker Bros. Pianos and Wilcox & White Organs" (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, B.F. Blakeslee, 186-?; Autograph note on back: "Do you want to sell your Phoenix Fire? And at what price? B. F. Blakeslee." (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, Benjamin Bliss & Company, 186-; "Silks, Dress Goods, Cloths, Cassimeres & Trimmings at the Lowest Market Prices. Umbrellas and Parasols Made and Repaired." (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Postcard, Blodgett & Clapp Company, 1895; "Dear Sir: Our Mr. Hungerford will take pleasure in calling upon you on or about May 28…." (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, Blue Label Café, 191-?; F. M. Franzen, Proprietor. "Fine Bottled Wines and Liquors A Specialty. Choice Brands Union-Made Cigars." (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, William boardman and Sons Company, 1908; "If those so-called Food Coffees don't agree with you, try Boardman's 'Gold Star' Coffee and get the Genuine Article." (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, William boardman and Sons Company, 19--; Three designs featuring Japanese children and animals (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, Bolles & Roberts, 185-?; "Portrait & Picture Frames, Window Cornices, Brackets, &c. Oil Paintings, French and English Engravings; English and French Looking Glass Plates Constantly on Hand." (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, Bond Press, Inc., 1996?; Oliver F. Johnson, President (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, Boston Branch tea and Grocery House, 1877; "Go to the Boston Branch Tea and Grocery House to buy your Flour!" Five designs featuring Japanee children. (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, Boston Furniture Company, 1878; Julius A. Kellogg, Manager. Two different pictorial designs. (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, Boston Furniture Company, 187-?; Julius A. Kellogg, Manager. "Furniture, Bedding, Feathers, Mirror, Etc." Two designs featuring girls. (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, Boston Shoe Store, 18--?; J. W. Eldridge, Proprietor. "A Perfect Fit at the Boston Shoe Store." Cut-out in the shape of a boot (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, Boston Square Dealing One-Price Clothing House, 187-; "This is a branch of a Large Wholesale House in Boston." (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, W.H. Brainard, 18--; "Repairing Promptly Done." (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Postcard, C.S. Brewer & Company, 1885; "We quote New Norfolk Potatoes…. Send us your orders…" (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Postcard, C.S. Brewer & Company, 1890; "We quote you Lemons…. Oranges…. Potatoes…. Onions…. Cabbage…. " (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Postcard, C.S. Brewer & Company, 1892; "We have notice from Fort Valley, Ga., of a Shipment of a Car Load of Elberta Peaches…." (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, O.H. Briggs, 186-; "Breakfast Cocoa" "Caramels" "Imported Chocolate" "Fine Bon-Bons." Three different designs (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Postcard, Briggs Paint Company, 1938; "Fit & Style in our Footwear" (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, Bronner and Company, 18--; Three designs each featuring a boy and a map (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, S.M. Bronson, 187-?; "Poultry and Game a Specialty." (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, W.S. Bronson, 1880; Two-sided puzzle card: "Every Universal Clothes Wringer is Warranted." (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Bookmark, Brown and Gross, 187-?; Bookmark with design featuring birds (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, Brown, Thompson[sic] and Company, 1880; Four "American Puzzle Cards." (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, Brown, Thomson and Company (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, Brown, Thomson and Company, 189-?; Two cards with different designs featuring berries: "Clearing Book Sale" "Special Trade Sale of Books" (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Stamp, Brown, Thomson and Company, 1915?; "Fit & Style in our Footwear" (Box 8, Folder B)
  - Trade card, C.W. Brown, 185-?; "Fresh & Salt Meat, Vegetables, Etc." "All kinds of Ship Stores up at short notice." (Box 8, Folder B)